calastrology.com 2018-08-04

# 

The California Astrology Association (CAA) respects your privacy and the security of your personal information. 

For this reason, we have updated our Privacy Policy (“Policy”) as of May 25, 2018. 

It describes the information that we collect, how we use it and what choices you have. This Policy applies when you access our websites and mobile applications, contact us by phone, email, and chat or connect with us in any other manner, including in our social media channels. 

At certain times, we may provide additional policies to which you must agree separately. 

### Privacy Policy

We are a Yahoo Store Merchant. Our website is hosted by Yahoo Store. We strictly adhere to Yahoo’s Yahoo! Store Guidelines and Terms of Service. 

Yahoo! Store currently hosts over 24,000 different e-commerce sites. It’s the industry leader, and is dependable, safe, and trustworthy. 

### Security

Any transaction you make with us is secure. The credit card and ordering information you provide to us when purchasing our products or services are protected by Yahoo!'s secure servers, using industry-standard SSL encryption. This ensures that your personal information is kept confidential as it travels over the internet. 

Additionally, we use the McAfee Secure service, which continually monitors our website for security and certifies that it is indeed safe to shop with us. Please click on the McAfee Secure logo for more information and to verify our certification: 

### Information We Collect

_Information that you share with California Astrology Association:_

We collect and store the information that you provide to us. For example, you may provide information to us when you place an order or create an account on our websites, apply for a job, enter a sweepstakes or contest, join our mailing list, take a survey, or connect with one of our customer service representatives. Types of information that you may provide to us include, for example: your name, mailing address, telephone number, email address, payment information, date of birth or pictures. If you choose to share information on our social media sites, including the posting of any pictures, please read our Content Submission Terms and Conditions. 

You may also share information about a gift recipient if you purchase a gift card or send a package to someone other than yourself. 

_Additional information that we may receive:_

We also collect and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us via the internet. Types of information that we may gather through this automatic process include your device location, IP address, browsing history and purchase history. Please see the Cookies and Pixel Tags section for additional information. 

_Information we gather from other sources:_

To best serve you, we may combine the information that you provide to us and the information that is gathered automatically with data that is publicly available and data that we receive from other reputable sources, such as California Astrology Association’s credit card issuer. This includes such things as change of address information and demographic information. We work with these third parties to help us add to, verify, or correct the information that we store. 

**For E.U. Residents Only:** Please note that if you are a resident of the European Union, we will only collect additional information via cookies and other online tools if you agree to its collection, and the sharing of such information is subject to your specific consent. 

### Updating Your Information

If any of your information has changed and you would like to update your customer information (name, address, telephone number, and email address), please contact us. 

To protect your privacy, we will need to validate your identity before we update or review your information. 

### Why We Collect Your Information

We collect this information for many reasons. For example, the information that you provide to California Astrology Association enables us to: process your order, contact you about the status of your order, post your product review, save your purchase history, manage your online account, send you promotional emails, and provide you with the best possible customer service. 

The additional information that we receive from you and gather from other sources allows us to serve you better and improve the overall shopping experience for all of our customers. For example, this type of information enables us to: improve the design of our website, understand shopping preferences, serve advertisements that we think may be of interest to customers, and improve upon the content of our promotional emails, our merchandise selection, and our customer service. 

### Sharing Your Information

We partner with third-party companies that provide certain services for us and we share your information with these companies, so that they can perform those services on our behalf. We have partners who help us with things such as shipping, name and address verification, email distribution, market research, survey distribution, California Astrology Association advertising across third-party platforms, promotions management, fraud protection & investigation, and payment processing (to view PayPal’s privacy policy, please visit https://www.paypal.com/privacy). 

We partner with third parties, such as Facebook and Google, to serve you ads that we think may interest you. These third parties may combine the information we share with them with information already in their possession; they may also offer you choices about which ads you see on their platforms. 

We also partner with third-party vendors that use analytics data for a variety of purposes such as to improve the design and content of our websites, to help us learn which pages are most attractive to all of our visitors and what promotions visitors like to see, and to gauge the success of our advertising campaigns. One such vendor is Google Analytics. Please click here for more information about how data is collected and processed in connection with the Google Analytics service: https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/. 

We work closely with our partners to ensure that your privacy is respected and protected and require these third parties keep your personal information secure and confidential. We may allow some of our third-party partners to use the information we share with them for their own purposes, but only if it is anonymized and aggregated, so that it cannot be linked back to any individual or California Astrology Association. 

On rare occasions, we may disclose specific information upon governmental request, in response to a court order, when we have a good faith belief that we are required to do so by law, or where otherwise permitted by law. 

We may also share your personal information in connection with or during the negotiation of any merger, financing, acquisition or dissolution transaction or proceeding involving sale, transfer, divestiture, or disclosure of all or a portion of our company or assets. If another company acquires our company or assets, that company may possess the personal information collected by us and will assume the consents and responsibilities regarding your personal information as described in this Policy. 

### Cookies and Pixel Tags

We gather information about how visitors navigate through our website by using clickstream data gathered with "cookies" and other online tools such as "pixel tags." 

A cookie is a small data file stored by your web browser on your computer. Session cookies are erased when the user closes the web browser or browser tab. Persistent cookies remain on your hard drive until they expire or are deleted. 

Some cookies are necessary for our website’s functionality and enable you to place an item in your online shopping bag and to place an order on our website. Other cookies allow us to enhance and personalize your online shopping experience, so the information you receive is more relevant to you. Here are some examples of what cookies allows us to do: remember what items are in your shopping bag, recognize you when you return to our website, enable faster checkout if you have created an account at llbean.com, analyze how our customers navigate our website and which products they search for, and deliver personalized marketing from California Astrology Association. If you set your browser to refuse all cookies, please contact us directly to place your order. 

We use pixel tags – tiny graphic images – to tell us what parts of our website you have visited or to measure the effectiveness of any searches you may do on our website. Pixel tags also enable us to send you email in a format you can read and let us know when you have opened an email message from us. 

Some of our third-party vendors may also use cookies or other online tools such as pixel tags on our website. 

We also contract with third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our behalf across the internet. To do this, they will collect information about your visits to our website and your interaction with our products and services. They may also use information about your visits to this and other websites to target advertisements. These targeted advertisements may appear on other sites that you visit. This information is collected using a cookie or pixel tag – industry standard technology used by most websites. 

**For E.U. Residents Only:** Please note that if you are a European Union resident, we only use non-essential cookies and pixel tags (those we use for enhancement and personalization) when you opt-in to allowing for their use. However, there are some cookies that must remain in order for our website to function property (essential cookies) and these will remain in use even if you do not opt-in to our use of non-essential cookies. 

### Your Choices

We want you to be satisfied with our use of your information and the communications you receive from us. We are happy to honor your preference requests. 

If you feel you hear from us too often or you prefer not to hear from us at all, whether by mail or by email, we are happy to change your preferences. You can unsubscribe from our email updates using the link provided in each email. Please keep in mind that if you choose not to receive these promotional emails, you will continue to receive emails from us about recent transactions, including orders and returns. 

You can also contact us directly, so that we may make the changes on your behalf. So that we can be sure to identify you correctly, please provide us with your exact name and address or the mailing label from your catalog. Because mailings and promotional emails are planned in advance, it may take several weeks for your request to become effective. 

To opt-out of direct personalized advertising on the Internet from California Astrology Association, please contact us. 

If you choose to opt-out of direct personalized advertising, you may still see advertisements on the internet from California Astrology Association, however, such advertisements were not generated by use of your personal information. 

**For Canadian Residents Only:** If you are a resident of Canada and you would like to take advantage of any of your rights under the Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act (PIPEDA) please contact California Astrology Association. 

**For E.U. Residents Only:** If you are a resident of the European Union and you would like to take advantage of any of your rights under the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), such as your Right to Erasure (otherwise known as the “Right to be Forgotten”) please contact California Astrology Association. For additional information related to EU residents, please see the European Union Residents section of this policy. 

### Privacy of Children

Protecting the rights of children is very important to California Astrology Association. Our website is not intended for use by children under the age of 13 and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 18, you may only use Calastrology.com with the help of a parent or guardian. 

### Links to Other Website

Occasionally we provide links to other websites to enhance functionality and the shopping experience. These sites operate independently of California Astrology Association and have established their own privacy and security policies. If you choose to navigate to another website through our websites, we strongly encourage you to review the policies of those websites also. 

### Information Security

California Astrology Association maintains your information securely. It is our intent to protect against the loss, misuse, alteration, or unauthorized access of information that we have collected from you or received from a partner. In order to protect it securely, we use a variety of current technologies and processes and are always working to stay current with trends in Information Security. It is our practice to use encryption or hashing whenever we receive or transmit your sensitive information. 

### Policy Changes

If our practices change, we will make the necessary changes to this privacy policy. We will notify you of a change to the policy by updating the date above. We encourage you to review our privacy policy periodically. 

**For EU Residents Only:** Please note that if our practices change, we will notify you of the change and, if necessary, obtain new consent. 

### European Union Residents

We will only collect your information from non-essential cookies if you consent to that use. 

We will only use the information you provide to us, such as the information you provide when placing an order, for our own marketing purposes if you consent to that use. 

If you wish to take advantage of any of your rights pursuant to the European Union Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), such as the Right to Erasure (otherwise known as the “Right to be Forgotten”), please contact us. 

If you feel our customer service has not appropriately responded to your request pursuant to the GDPR, you may contact California Astrology Association ’s Data Protection Officer (DPO) directly. Please send all correspondence to: Data Protection Officer, P.O. Box 8005, Canoga Park, CA 91309, or by email to info@calastrology.com. 

### Contact Us

You are always welcome to contact us about your privacy, whether you have questions or wish to provide any feedback. Our office hours are Monday – Friday, 10AM – 4PM Pacific time. 

by email: info@calastrology.com  
by mail: California Astrology Association, P.O. Box 8005, Canoga Park, CA 91309  
by phone: U.S. and Canada: (818) 340-9007  
by Fax: (818)340-9193

To make sure we continue to offer the best service possible, your communication with California Astrology Association may be monitored for quality assurance. 

If you would like to be removed from our email newsletter mailing list, please click the unsubscribe button in any of our four weekly emails. 

### Additional information from Yahoo!

Third-Party Web Beacons: We use third-party web beacons from Yahoo! to help analyze where visitors go and what they do while visiting our website. Yahoo! may also use anonymous information about your visits to this and other websites in order to improve its products and services and provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by Yahoo!, [click here](https://reports.web.analytics.yahoo.com/optout,OptOut.vm?domain=a.analytics.yahoo.com).
